Deception hits home.
Inconceivable is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Jonathan Baker.
A mother looks to escape her abusive past by moving to a new town where
she befriends another mother, who grows suspicious of her.
Brian, played by Nicolas Cage.
Angela, played by Gina Gershon.
Katie, played by Nicky Whelan.
Donna, played by Faye Dunaway.
Linda, played by Natalie Eva Marie.
Dr. Weisman, played by James Van Patten.
Inconceivable is a 2017 American thriller film directed by
Jonathan Baker and written by Chloe King.
It stars Gina Gershon, Faye Dunaway, Nicolas Cage,
Nicky Whelan and Natalie Eva Marie.
The film was released on June 30, 2017, by Lionsgate Premiere.
The tone is emotional and intense.